top10songs.com 2011-12-31

# Top 10 Songs - Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY**

At Top 10 Songs we are committed to protecting your privacy. Users do not have to register or disclose any personal information in order to gain access to Top 10 Songs. We are dedicated to keeping your experience with us secure, enjoyable and easy. The following discloses our information gathering and disclosure practices. 

**Personal Information**

Top 10 Songs collects personally identifiable information only during voluntary user surveys, contests or emailed submissions. The information we collect helps us to better program our site. We do not send unsolicited communication to our users. Top 10 Songs may provide aggregate statistics about our users, traffic patterns and related site information to reputable third party vendors, but these statistics will not include personally identifiable information. Top 10 Songs does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others. 

**Security**

Although Top 10 Songs uses all reasonable efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information, transmissions made by means of the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. Top 10 Songs will have no liability for disclosure of personally identifiable information due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties. 

**Outside Links**

Top 10 Songs contains links to other websites. Top 10 Songs is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites. 

**Advertising & Cookies**

Top 10 Songs uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [ click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). While we do not use cookies on our sites, ads from advertisers may contain cookies. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on your visit to our sites and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). Users will be able to use all features of Top 10 Songs whether or not they have disabled cookies on their system. 

**Consent**

By using this website, you signify your consent with the Top 10 Songs Privacy Policy. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

Back To Top    |   [Contact Us](mailto:info@top10songs.com)    |   [Home](http://www.top10songs.com/)

Copyright © 2011 Top 10 Songs. All rights reserved.
